# Cecilia Lanza Floquet Felix

Brasileira, casada, 26 anos

Telefone: +55 11 95447-5699 / E-mail: ceciliafloquet@hotmail.com

# FORMAÇÃO

 Graduação: Direito (OAB 2012) - Faculdade Baiana de Ciências - Maurício de Nassau -Conclusão 2011.2

Graduação: Gestão de Recursos Humanos – Unijorge – Conclusão 2015.2

### EXPERIÊNCIA PROFISSIONAL

# 02/2013 – 04/2014 – Escritório de Advocacia Bertoli

Cargo: Advogada.

Principais atividades: Audiências trabalhistas, petições eletrônicas, organização de prazos, atendimento ao cliente, criação e manutenção de planilhas, pagamento e recebimento de contas e relatórios.

### • 07/2012 - 06/2014 - Tribunal de Justiça do Estado da Bahia

Cargo: Advogada e supervisora voluntária do balcão de justiça e cidadania.

Principais atividades: Supervisionar o funcionamento do balcão e os seus membros, mediar às partes nos acordos, orientar juridicamente as pessoas e conferir os acordos realizados no balcão.

## • 01/2010 - 12/2011 - Tribunal de Justiça do Estado da Bahia

Cargo: Estagiária de Direito - Coordenação dos balcões de Justiça e cidadania.

Principais atividades: Cadastrar dados dos processos judiciais, esquematizar sistema de acompanhamento dos processos em andamento, examinar processos diversos, fazer peças e pareceres, receber e emitir processos, fazer expedição de processos, documentos e correspondências, organizar arquivo de processos, autuar processos, elaborar sentenças, ofícios, documentos, correspondências e publicações, orientações às partes.

# • 04/2009 – 12/2009 – Tribunal de Jusiça do Estado da Bahia

Cargo: Estagiária de Direito - Balcão de Justiça e Cidadania de Sussuarana

Principais atividades: Atendimento e orientação às partes, esquematizar sistema de acompanhamento dos acordos em andamento, receber e emitir acordos, fazer expedição de documentos e correspondência, organizar arquivos de atendimento e mediação, elaboração ofícios, documentos, correspondências e relatórios.

#### **CURSOS**

- Curso de Prática Previdenciária no Regime Geral de Previdência Social
- Curso de Prática Trabalhista

# CONHECIMENTOS

- Pacote office
- Windows
- Internet

# Cecilia Lanza Floquet Felix

102-1111 Seymour Street, Vancôver, BC

ceciliafloquet@gmail.com

604 518 1850

## Summary

An innovative Prosecutor for more than four years in achievement in Family court. I am also Attorney offering skill in innovative problem solving and finding unique theories, ideas and solutions to create effectual case arguments. Works aggreessively to achieve continued success.

# **Highlights**

- Analytical and Problem Solving
- · Critical Reasoning
- Oral Communication and Listening
- · specializing in family law

### **Experience**

 02/2013 - 04/2014 - Bertoli Law Office Lawyer

Labor audits, electronic petitions, organization of deadlines, customer service, creation and maintenance of spreadsheets, payment and receipt of accounts and reports.

• 07/2012 - 06/2014 - Court of Justice of the State of Bahia Lawyer and supervisor

Supervise the operation of the counter and its members, mediate the parties to the agreements, provide legal advice to the people and check the agreements made at the counter.

• 01/2010 - 12/2011 - Court of Justice of the State of Bahia Law intern - Coordination of the Justice and Citizenship counters.

To register data of the judicial processes, to systemaze system of follow-up of the processes in process, to examine diverse processes, to make parts and opinions, to receive and to issue processes, to make dispatch of processes, documents and correspondences, to organize file of processes, to authenticate processes, to elaborate sentences, , documents, correspondence and publications, guidelines to the parties.

• 04/2009 - 12/2009 - Court of Justice of the State of Bahia law intern - Justice and Citizenship Counter of Sussuarana

Attendance and orientation to the parties, outline the system of follow-up of agreements in progress, receive and issue agreements, dispatch documents and correspondence, organize attendance and mediation files, draw up offices, documents, correspondence and reports.

#### **E**DUCATION

• Bachelor of Law - Maurício de Nassau University

DEAR SIR OR MADAM,

PLEASE CONSIDER MY APPLICATION FOR THE FAMILY LAW LITIGATOR. I AM CONFIDENT THAT THIS POSITION MATCHES WITH MY INTERESTS, EDUCATION AND EXPERIENCE AS YOU CAN SEE BELOW.

I have my jury's doctorate from Mauricio de Nassau University. I have been working with court of justice of Salvador as a corporate legal practitioner. Here I was involved with lot of the work on research and writing briefs. Apart from this, I have spent significant amounts of time and resource on legal precedent and write research findings. I am capable of handling stresses that are involved in legal cases. Moreover, I am also good at arguing for my clients and can prove my points to the judge.

I AM A SELF AND FAST LEARNING, WILLING TO IMPROVE MY SKILLS IN BENEFIT OF A COMPANY. I BELIEVE I AM A GOOD FIT FOR YOUR COMPANY BECAUSE I AM PASSIONATE ABOUT NEW TECHNOLOGIES AND INNOVATION. I HAVE INTEREST IN GROW IN A COMPANY.

Please review my resume and consider my request for an interview to discuss how my educational qualifications and skills would benefit your company. You can reach me at email(ceciliafloquet@gmail.com) and phone(6045181850).

I LOOK FORWARD TO MEETING YOU FOR AN INTERVIEW WHERE WE CAN DISCUSS MORE DETAILS.

SINCERELY,

CECILIA FLOQUET